PM5CTL0 {Register}
	Power Mode 5 Control Register 0.
	Chapter: 2.3.8
	Table: Table 2-23. PM5CTL0 Register Description.
	@ LOCKLPM5
		Bit: 0
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: Lock I/O pin configuration upon entry to or exit from LPMx.5. When power is applied to the device, this bit, once set, can only be cleared by the user or via another power cycle. Note: This bit was formerly named LOCKIO, and some application reports and code examples may continue to use this terminology. 0b = I/O pin configuration is not locked and defaults to its reset condition. 1b = I/O pin configuration remains locked. Pin state is held during LPMx.5 entry and exit. voltage level triggers a POR.
	Toplevel: <<PM5CTL0 {Register}>>
	@
