PMMIFG {Register}
	Power Management Module Interrupt Flag Register.
	Chapter: 2.3.4
	Table: Table2-21.PMMIFG Register Description.
	@ PMMLPM5IFG
		Bit: 15
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: LPMx.5 flag. This bit is set if the system was in LPMx.5 before. The bit is cleared by software or by reading the reset vector word. A power failure on the DVCC domain clears the bit. 0b = No interrupt pending 1b = Interrupt pending
	Toplevel: <<PMMIFG {Register}>>
	@ SVSLIFG
		Bit: 13
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVS low-side interrupt flag. The bit is cleared by software or by reading the reset vector word. 0b = No interrupt pending 1b = Interrupt pending
	Toplevel: <<PMMIFG {Register}>>
	@ SVSHIFG
		Bit: 12
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVS high-side interrupt flag. The bit is cleared by software or by reading the reset vector word. 0b = No interrupt pending 1b = Interrupt pending
	Toplevel: <<PMMIFG {Register}>>
	@ PMMPORIFG
		Bit: 10
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: PMM software power-on reset interrupt flag. This interrupt flag is set if a software POR is triggered. The bit is cleared by software or by reading the reset vector word, SYSRSTIV. 0b = No interrupt pending 1b = Interrupt pending
	Toplevel: <<PMMIFG {Register}>>
	@ PMMRSTIFG
		Bit: 9
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: PMM reset pin interrupt flag. This interrupt flag is set if the RST/NMI pin is the reset source. The bit is cleared by software or by reading the reset vector word. 0b = No interrupt pending 1b = Interrupt pending
	Toplevel: <<PMMIFG {Register}>>
	@ PMMBORIFG
		Bit: 8
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: PMM software brownout reset interrupt flag. This interrupt flag is set if a software BOR (PMMSWBOR) is triggered. The bit is cleared by software or by reading the reset vector word, SYSRSTIV. 0b = No interrupt pending 1b = Interrupt pending
	Toplevel: <<PMMIFG {Register}>>
	@ SVMHVLRIFG
		Bit: 6
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVM high-side voltage level reached interrupt flag. The bit is cleared by software or by reading the reset vector (SVSHPE = 1) word or by reading the interrupt vector (SVSHPE = 0) word. 0b = No interrupt pending 1b = Interrupt pending
	Toplevel: <<PMMIFG {Register}>>
	@ SVMHIFG
		Bit: 5
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVM high-side interrupt flag. The bit is cleared by software. 0b = No interrupt pending 1b = Interrupt pending voltage reached level. The voltage levels are defined in the device-specific data sheet. Note: SVSMHRRL must always be equal or larger than SVSHRVL.
	Toplevel: <<PMMIFG {Register}>>
	@ SVSMHDLYIFG
		Bit: 4
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVS and SVM high-side delay expired interrupt flag. This interrupt flag is set if the delay element expired. The bit is cleared by software or by reading the interrupt vector word. 0b = No interrupt pending 1b = Interrupt pending
	Toplevel: <<PMMIFG {Register}>>
	@ SVMLVLRIFG
		Bit: 2
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVM low-side voltage level reached interrupt flag. The bit is cleared by software or by reading the reset vector (SVSLPE = 1) word or by reading the interrupt vector (SVSLPE = 0) word. 0b = No interrupt pending 1b = Interrupt pending
	Toplevel: <<PMMIFG {Register}>>
	@ SVMLIFG
		Bit: 1
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVM low-side interrupt flag. The bit is cleared by software. 0b = No interrupt pending 1b = Interrupt pending
	Toplevel: <<PMMIFG {Register}>>
	@ SVSMLDLYIFG
		Bit: 0
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVS and SVM low-side delay expired interrupt flag. This interrupt flag is set if the delay element expired. The bit is cleared by software or by reading the interrupt vector word. 0b = No interrupt pending 1b = Interrupt pending
	Toplevel: <<PMMIFG {Register}>>
	@