RCCTL0 {Register}
	RAM Controller Control 0 Register.
	Chapter: 9.3.1
	Table: Table9-2. RCCTL0 Register Description.
	@ RCKEY
		Bit: 15-8
		Type: RW
		Reset: 69h
		Description: RAM controller key. Always read as 69h. Must be written as 5Ah, otherwise the RAMCTL write is ignored.
	Toplevel: <<RCCTL0 {Register}>>
	@ RCRS7OFF
		Bit: 7
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: RAM controller RAM sector 7 off. Setting the bit to 1 turns off the RAM sector 7. All data of the RAM sector 7 is lost. See the device-specific data sheet to find the the number of RAM sectors available along with their respective address ranges and sizes.
	Toplevel: <<RCCTL0 {Register}>>
	@ RCRS6OFF
		Bit: 6
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: RAM controller RAM sector 6 off. Setting the bit to 1 turns off the RAM sector 6. All data of the RAM sector 6 is lost. See the device-specific data sheet to find the the number of RAM sectors available along with their respective address ranges and sizes.
	Toplevel: <<RCCTL0 {Register}>>
	@ RCRS5OFF
		Bit: 5
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: RAM controller RAM sector 5 off. Setting the bit to 1 turns off the RAM sector 5. All data of the RAM sector 5 is lost. See the device-specific data sheet to find the the number of RAM sectors available along with their respective address ranges and sizes.
	Toplevel: <<RCCTL0 {Register}>>
	@ RCRS4OFF
		Bit: 4
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: RAM controller RAM sector 4 off. Setting the bit to 1 turns off the RAM sector 4. All data of the RAM sector 4 is lost. See the device-specific data sheet to find the the number of RAM sectors available along with their respective address ranges and sizes.
	Toplevel: <<RCCTL0 {Register}>>
	@ RCRS3OFF
		Bit: 3
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: RAM controller RAM sector 3 off. Setting the bit to 1 turns off the RAM sector 3. All data of the RAM sector 3 is lost. See the device-specific data sheet to find the the number of RAM sectors available along with their respective address ranges and sizes.
	Toplevel: <<RCCTL0 {Register}>>
	@ RCRS2OFF
		Bit: 2
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: RAM controller RAM sector 2 off. Setting the bit to 1 turns off the RAM sector 2. All data of the RAM sector 2 is lost. See the device-specific data sheet to find the the number of RAM sectors available along with their respective address ranges and sizes.
	Toplevel: <<RCCTL0 {Register}>>
	@ RCRS1OFF
		Bit: 1
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: RAM controller RAM sector 1 off. Setting the bit to 1 turns off the RAM sector 1. All data of the RAM sector 1 is lost. See the device-specific data sheet to find the the number of RAM sectors available along with their respective address ranges and sizes.
	Toplevel: <<RCCTL0 {Register}>>
	@ RCRS0OFF
		Bit: 0
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: RAM controller RAM sector 0 off. Setting the bit to 1 turns off the RAM sector 0. All data of the RAM sector 0 is lost. See the device-specific data sheet to find the the number of RAM sectors available along with their respective address ranges and sizes.
	Toplevel: <<RCCTL0 {Register}>>
	@