SFRIFG1 {Register}
	Interrupt Flag Register
	Chapter: 1.14.2
	Table: Table1-13. SFRIFG1 Register Description
	@ JMBOUTIFG
		Bit: 7
		Type: RW
		Reset: 1h
		Description: JTAG mailbox output interrupt flag 0b = No interrupt pending. When in 16-bit mode (JMBMODE = 0), this bit is cleared automatically when JMBO0 has been written with a new message to the JTAG module by the CPU. When in 32-bit mode (JMBMODE = 1), this bit is cleared automatically when both JMBO0 and JMBO1 have been written with new messages to the JTAG module by the CPU. This bit is also cleared when the associated vector in SYSUNIV has been read. 1b = Interrupt pending, JMBO registers are ready for new messages. In 16-bit mode (JMBMODE = 0), JMBO0 has been received by the JTAG module and is ready for a new message from the CPU. In 32-bit mode (JMBMODE = 1) , JMBO0 and JMBO1 have been received by the JTAG module and are ready for new messages from the CPU.
	Toplevel: <<SFRIFG1 {Register}>>
	@ JMBINIFG
		Bit: 6
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: JTAG mailbox input interrupt flag 0b = No interrupt pending. When in 16-bit mode (JMBMODE = 0), this bit is cleared automatically when JMBI0 is read by the CPU. When in 32-bit mode (JMBMODE = 1), this bit is cleared automatically when both JMBI0 and JMBI1 have been read by the CPU. This bit is also cleared when the associated vector in SYSUNIV has been read 1b = Interrupt pending, a message is waiting in the JMBIN registers. In 16-bit mode (JMBMODE = 0) when JMBI0 has been written by the JTAG module. In 32-bit mode (JMBMODE = 1) when JMBI0 and JMBI1 have been written by the JTAG module.
	Toplevel: <<SFRIFG1 {Register}>>
	@ NMIIFG
		Bit: 4
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: NMI pin interrupt flag 0b = No interrupt pending 1b = Interrupt pending
	Toplevel: <<SFRIFG1 {Register}>>
	@ VMAIFG
		Bit: 3
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: Vacant memory access interrupt flag 0b = No interrupt pending 1b = Interrupt pending
	Toplevel: <<SFRIFG1 {Register}>>
	@ OFIFG
		Bit: 1
		Type: RW
		Reset: 1h
		Description: Oscillator fault interrupt flag 0b = No interrupt pending 1b = Interrupt pending
	Toplevel: <<SFRIFG1 {Register}>>
	@ WDTIFG
		Bit: 0
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: Watchdog timer interrupt flag. In watchdog mode, WDTIFG will self clear upon a watchdog timeout event. The SYSRSTIV can be read to determine if the reset was caused by a watchdog timeout event. In interval mode, WDTIFG is reset automatically by servicing the interrupt, or can be reset by software. Because other bits in ~IFG1 may be used for other modules, it is recommended to set or clear WDTIFG by using BIS.B or BIC.B instructions, rather than MOV.B or CLR.B instructions. 0b = No interrupt pending 1b = Interrupt pending
	Toplevel: <<SFRIFG1 {Register}>>
	@