SR
	The 16-bit Status Register (SR, also called R2), used as a source or destination register, can only be used in register mode addressed with word instructions. The remaining combinations of addressing modes are used to support the constant generator. Figure 6-9 shows the SR bits. Do not write 20-bit values to the SR. Unpredictable operation can result.
	Chapter: 6.3.3
	Table: Table 6-1. SR Bit Description
	@ V
		Description: Overflow. This bit is set when the result of an arithmetic operation overflows the signed-variable range. ADD(.B), ADDX(.B,.A), Set when: ADDC(.B), ADDCX(.B.A), positive + positive = negative ADDA negative + negative = positive otherwise reset SUB(.B), SUBX(.B,.A), Set when: SUBC(.B),SUBCX(.B,.A), positive – negative = negative negative – positive = positive SUBA, CMP(.B), otherwise reset CMPX(.B,.A), CMPA
	Toplevel: <<SR>>
	@ SCG1
		Description: System clock generator 1. This bit may be used to enable or disable functions in the clock system depending on the device family; for example, DCO bias enable or disable.
	Toplevel: <<SR>>
	@ SCG0
		Description: System clock generator 0. This bit may be used to enable or disable functions in the clock system depending on the device family; for example, FLL enable or disable.
	Toplevel: <<SR>>
	@ OSCOFF
		Description: Oscillator off. When this bit is set, it turns off the LFXT1 crystal oscillator when LFXT1CLK is not used for MCLK or SMCLK.
	Toplevel: <<SR>>
	@ CPUOFF
		Description: CPU off. When this bit is set, it turns off the CPU.
	Toplevel: <<SR>>
	@ GIE
		Description: General interrupt enable. When this bit is set, it enables maskable interrupts. When it is reset, all maskable interrupts are disabled.
	Toplevel: <<SR>>
	@ N
		Description: Negative. This bit is set when the result of an operation is negative and cleared when the result is positive.
	Toplevel: <<SR>>
	@ Z
		Description: Zero. This bit is set when the result of an operation is 0 and cleared when the result is not 0.
	Toplevel: <<SR>>
	@ C
		Description: Carry. This bit is set when the result of an operation produced a carry and cleared when no carry occurred.
	Toplevel: <<SR>>
	@