SVSMIO {Register}
	SVSIN and SVMOUT Control Register.
	Chapter: 2.3.5
	Table: Table 2-20. SVSMIO Register Description.
	@ SVMHVLROE
		Bit: 12
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVM high-side voltage level reached output enable. If this bit is set, the SVMHVLRIFG bit is output to the device SVMOUT pin. The device-specific port logic has to be configured accordingly.
	Toplevel: <<SVSMIO {Register}>>
	@ SVMHOE
		Bit: 11
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVM high-side output enable. If this bit is set, the SVMHIFG bit is output to the device SVMOUT pin. The device-specific port logic has to be configured accordingly.
	Toplevel: <<SVSMIO {Register}>>
	@ SVMOUTPOL
		Bit: 5
		Type: RW
		Reset: 1h
		Description: SVMOUT pin polarity. If this bit is set, SVMOUT is active high. An error condition is signaled by a 1 at SVMOUT. If SVMOUTPOL is cleared, the error condition is signaled by a 0 at the SVMOUT pin.
	Toplevel: <<SVSMIO {Register}>>
	@ SVMLVLROE
		Bit: 4
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVM low-side voltage level reached output enable. If this bit is set, the SVMLVLRIFG bit is output to the device SVMOUT pin. The device-specific port logic has to be configured accordingly.
	Toplevel: <<SVSMIO {Register}>>
	@ SVMLOE
		Bit: 3
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVM low-side output enable. If this bit is set, the SVMLIFG bit is output to the device SVMOUT pin. The device-specific port logic has to be configured accordingly.
	Toplevel: <<SVSMIO {Register}>>
	@