SVSMHCTL {Register}
	Supply Voltage Supervisor and Monitor High-Side Control Register
	Chapter: 2.3.3
	Table: Table 2-18.SVSMHCTL Register Description
	@ SVMHFP
		Bit: 15
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVM high-side full-performance mode. If this bit is set, the SVMH operates in full-performance mode. 0b = Normal mode. See the device-specific data sheet for response times. 1b = Full-performance mode. See the device-specific data sheet for response times.
	Toplevel: <<SVSMHCTL {Register}>>
	@ SVMHE
		Bit: 14
		Type: RW
		Reset: 1h
		Description: SVM high-side enable. If this bit is set, the SVMH is enabled.
	Toplevel: <<SVSMHCTL {Register}>>
	@ SVMHOVPE
		Bit: 12
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVM high-side overvoltage enable. If this bit is set, the SVMH overvoltage detection is enabled. If SVMHVLRPE is also set, a POR occurs on an overvoltage condition.
	Toplevel: <<SVSMHCTL {Register}>>
	@ SVSHFP
		Bit: 11
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVS high-side full-performance mode. If this bit is set, the SVSH operates in full- performance mode. 0b = Normal mode. See the device-specific data sheet for response times. 1b = Full-performance mode. See the device-specific data sheet for response times.
	Toplevel: <<SVSMHCTL {Register}>>
	@ SVSHE
		Bit: 10
		Type: RW
		Reset: 1h
		Description: SVS high-side enable. If this bit is set, the SVSH is enabled.
	Toplevel: <<SVSMHCTL {Register}>>
	@ SVSHRVL
		Bit: 9-8
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVS high-side reset voltage level. If DVCC falls short of the SVSH voltage level selected by SVSHRVL, a reset is triggered (if SVSHPE = 1). The voltage levels are defined in the device-specific data sheet. Note: SVSMHRRL must always be equal or larger than SVSHRVL.
	Toplevel: <<SVSMHCTL {Register}>>
	@ SVSMHACE
		Bit: 7
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVS and SVM high-side automatic control enable. If this bit is set, the low-power mode of the SVSH and SVMH circuits is under hardware control.
	Toplevel: <<SVSMHCTL {Register}>>
	@ SVSMHEVM
		Bit: 6
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVS and SVM high-side event mask. If this bit is set, the SVSH and SVMH events are masked. 0b = No events are masked. 1b = All events are masked.
	Toplevel: <<SVSMHCTL {Register}>>
	@ SVSHMD
		Bit: 4
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVS high-side mode. If this bit is set, the SVSH interrupt flag is set in LPM2, LPM3, and LPM4 in case of power-fail conditions. If this bit is not set, the SVSH interrupt is not set in LPM2, LPM3, and LPM4. Note: This bit also affects the control mode selection (see Table 2-5).
	Toplevel: <<SVSMHCTL {Register}>>
	@ SVSMHDLYST
		Bit: 3
		Type: R
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVS and SVM high-side delay status. If this bit is set, the SVSH and SVMH events are masked for some delay time. The delay time depends on the power mode of the SVSH and SVMH. If SVMHFP = 1 and SVSHFP = 1 (that is, full- performance mode), the delay is shorter. See the device-specific data sheet for details. The bit is cleared by hardware if the delay has expired.
	Toplevel: <<SVSMHCTL {Register}>>
	@ SVSMHRRL
		Bit: 2-0
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVS and SVM high-side reset release voltage level. These bits define the reset release voltage level of the SVSH. It is also used for the SVMH to define the voltage reached level. The voltage levels are defined in the device-specific data sheet. Note: SVSMHRRL must always be equal or larger than SVSHRVL.
	Toplevel: <<SVSMHCTL {Register}>>
	@