SVSMLCTL {Register}
	Supply Voltage Supervisor and Monitor Low-Side Control Register
	Chapter: 2.3.4
	Table: Table 2-19.SVSMLCTL Register Description
	@ SVMLFP
		Bit: 15
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVM low-side full-performance mode. If this bit is set, the SVML operates in full- performance mode. 0b = Normal mode. See the device-specific data sheet for response times. 1b = Full-performance mode. See the device-specific data sheet for response times.
	Toplevel: <<SVSMLCTL {Register}>>
	@ SVMLE
		Bit: 14
		Type: RW
		Reset: 1h
		Description: SVM low-side enable. If this bit is set, the SVML is enabled.
	Toplevel: <<SVSMLCTL {Register}>>
	@ SVMLOVPE
		Bit: 12
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVM low-side overvoltage enable. If this bit is set, the SVML overvoltage detection is enabled.
	Toplevel: <<SVSMLCTL {Register}>>
	@ SVSLFP
		Bit: 11
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVS low-side full-performance mode. If this bit is set, the SVSL operates in full- performance mode. 0b = Normal mode. See the device-specific data sheet for response times. 1b = Full-performance mode. See the device-specific data sheet for response times.
	Toplevel: <<SVSMLCTL {Register}>>
	@ SVSLE
		Bit: 10
		Type: RW
		Reset: 1h
		Description: SVS low-side enable. If this bit is set, the SVSL is enabled.
	Toplevel: <<SVSMLCTL {Register}>>
	@ SVSLRVL
		Bit: 9-8
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVS low-side reset voltage level. If V(CORE) falls short of the SVSL voltage level selected by SVSLRVL, a reset is triggered (if SVSLPE = 1). Note: SVSMLRRL must always be equal to or larger than SVSLRVL.
	Toplevel: <<SVSMLCTL {Register}>>
	@ SVSMLACE
		Bit: 7
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVS and SVM low-side automatic control enable. If this bit is set, the low-power mode of the SVSL and SVML circuits is under hardware control.
	Toplevel: <<SVSMLCTL {Register}>>
	@ SVSMLEVM
		Bit: 6
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVS and SVM low-side event mask. If this bit is set, the SVSL and SVML events are masked. 0b = No events are masked. 1b = All events are masked.
	Toplevel: <<SVSMLCTL {Register}>>
	@ SVSLMD
		Bit: 4
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVS low-side mode. If this bit is set, the SVSL interrupt flag is set in LPM2, LPM3 and LPM4 in case of power-fail conditions. If this bit is not set, the SVSL interrupt is not set in LPM2, LPM3, and LPM4. Note: This bit also affects the control mode selection (see Table 2-5).
	Toplevel: <<SVSMLCTL {Register}>>
	@ SVSMLDLYST
		Bit: 3
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVS and SVM low-side delay status. If this bit is set, the SVSL and SVML events are masked for a delay time. The delay time depends on the power mode of the SVSL and SVML. If SVMLFP = 1 and SVSLFP = 1 (that is, full-performance mode), the delay is shorter. The bit is cleared by hardware if the delay has expired.
	Toplevel: <<SVSMLCTL {Register}>>
	@ SVSMLRRL
		Bit: 2-0
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SVS and SVM low-side reset release voltage level. These bits define the reset release voltage level of the SVSL. It is also used for the SVML to define the voltage reached level. Note: SVSMLRRL must always be equal or larger than SVSLRVL.
	Toplevel: <<SVSMLCTL {Register}>>
	@