SYSBERRIV {Register}
	System Bus Error Interrupt Vector Register
	Chapter: 1.15.11
	Table: Table 1-27. SYSBERRIV Register Description
	@ SYSBERRIV
		Bit: 15-0
		Type: R
		Reset: 0h
		Description: System bus error interrupt vector. Generates a value that can be used as an address offset for fast interrupt service routine handling. Writing to this register clears all pending flags. 00h = No interrupt pending 02h = USB module timed out. Wait state time out of 8 clock cycles. 16 clock cycles only on the F552x and F551x devices. 04h = Reserved for future extensions 06h = Reserved for future extensions 08h = Reserved for future extensions
		Toplevel: <<SYSBERRIV {Register}>>
	@