SYSCTL {Register}
	SYS Control Register
	Chapter: 1.15.1
	Table: Table 1-17. SYSCTL Register Description
	@ SYSJTAGPIN
		Bit: 5
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: Dedicated JTAG pins enable. Setting this bit disables the shared functionality of the JTAG pins and permanently enables the JTAG function. This bit can be set only once. After it is set, it remains set until a BOR occurs. 0b = Shared JTAG pins (JTAG mode selectable by SBW sequence) 1b = Dedicated JTAG pins (explicit 4-wire JTAG mode selection)
	Toplevel: <<SYSCTL {Register}>>
	@ SYSBSLIND
		Bit: 4
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: BSL entry indication. This bit indicates a BSL entry sequence detected on the Spy-Bi-Wire pins. 0b = No BSL entry sequence detected 1b = BSL entry sequence detected
	Toplevel: <<SYSCTL {Register}>>
	@ SYSPMMPE
		Bit: 2
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: PMM access protect. This controls the accessibility of the PMM control registers. Once set to 1, it only can be cleared by a BOR. 0b = Access from anywhere in memory 1b = Access only from the protected BSL segments
	Toplevel: <<SYSCTL {Register}>>
	@ SYSRIVECT
		Bit: 0
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: RAM-based interrupt vectors 0b = Interrupt vectors generated with end address TOP of lower 64KB of flash, FFFFh 1b = Interrupt vectors generated with end address TOP of RAM
	Toplevel: <<SYSCTL {Register}>>
	@