SYSJMBC {Register}
	JTAG Mailbox Control Register
	Chapter: 1.15.3
	Table: Table 1-19. SYSJMBC Register Description
	@ JMBCLR1OFF
		Bit: 7
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: Incoming JTAG Mailbox 1 flag auto-clear disable 0b = JMBIN1FG cleared on read of JMB1IN register 1b = JMBIN1FG cleared by software
	Toplevel: <<SYSJMBC {Register}>>
	@ JMBCLR0OFF
		Bit: 6
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: Incoming JTAG Mailbox 0 flag auto-clear disable 0b = JMBIN0FG cleared on read of JMB0IN register 1b = JMBIN0FG cleared by software
	Toplevel: <<SYSJMBC {Register}>>
	@ JMBMODE
		Bit: 4
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: This bit defines the operation mode of JMB for JMBI0, JMBI1, JMBO0, and JMBO1. Before switching this bit, pad and flush out any partial content to avoid data drops. 0b = 16-bit transfers using JMBO0 and JMBI0 only 1b = 32-bit transfers using JMBI0, JMBI1, JMBO0, and JMBO1
	Toplevel: <<SYSJMBC {Register}>>
	@ JMBOUT1FG
		Bit: 3
		Type: RW
		Reset: 1h
		Description: Outgoing JTAG Mailbox 1 flag. This bit is cleared automatically when a message is written to the upper byte of JMBO1 or as word access (by the CPU, DMA,...) and is set after the message was read by JTAG. 0b = JMBO1 is not ready to receive new data. 1b = JMBO1 is ready to receive new data.
	Toplevel: <<SYSJMBC {Register}>>
	@ JMBOUT0FG
		Bit: 2
		Type: RW
		Reset: 1h
		Description: Outgoing JTAG Mailbox 0 flag. This bit is cleared automatically when a message is written to the upper byte of JMBO0 or as word access (by the CPU, DMA,...) and is set after the message was read by JTAG. 0b = JMBO0 is not ready to receive new data. 1b = JMBO0 is ready to receive new data.
	Toplevel: <<SYSJMBC {Register}>>
	@ JMBIN1FG
		Bit: 1
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: Incoming JTAG Mailbox 1 flag. This bit is set when a new message (provided by JTAG) is available in JMBI1. This flag is cleared automatically on read of JMBI1 when JMBCLR1OFF = 0 (auto clear mode). On JMBCLR1OFF = 1, JMBIN1FG needs to be cleared by software. 0b = JMBI1 has no new data. 1b = JMBI1 has new data available.
	Toplevel: <<SYSJMBC {Register}>>
	@ JMBIN0FG
		Bit: 0
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: Incoming JTAG Mailbox 0 flag. This bit is set when a new message (provided by JTAG) is available in JMBI0. This flag is cleared automatically on read of JMBI0 when JMBCLR0OFF = 0 (auto clear mode). On JMBCLR0OFF = 1, JMBIN0FG needs to be cleared by software. 0b = JMBI1 has no new data. 1b = JMBI1 has new data available.
	Toplevel: <<SYSJMBC {Register}>>
	@