SYSSNIV {Register}
	System NMI Vector Register
	Chapter: 1.15.9
	Table: Table 1-25. SYSSNIV Register Description
	@ SYSSNIV
		Bit: 15-0
		Type: R
		Reset: 0h
		Description: System NMI vector. Generates a value that can be used as address offset for fast interrupt service routine handling. Writing to this register clears all pending system NMI flags. 00h = No interrupt pending 02h = SVMLIFG interrupt pending (highest priority) 04h = SVMHIFG interrupt pending 06h = SVSMLDLYIFG interrupt pending 08h = SVSMHDLYIFG interrupt pending 0Ah = VMAIFG interrupt pending 0Ch = JMBINIFG interrupt pending 0Eh = JMBOUTIFG interrupt pending 10h = SVMLVLRIFG interrupt pending 12h = SVMHVLRIFG interrupt pending 14h = Reserved
	Toplevel: <<SYSSNIV {Register}>>
	@