SYSUNIV {Register}
	User NMI Vector Register
	Chapter: 1.15.8
	Table: Table 1-24. SYSUNIV Register Description
	@ SYSUNIV
		Bit: 15-0
		Type: R
		Reset: 0h
		Description: User NMI vector. Generates a value that can be used as address offset for fast interrupt service routine handling. Writing to this register clears all pending user NMI flags. 00h = No interrupt pending 02h = NMIIFG interrupt pending (highest priority) 04h = OFIFG interrupt pending 06h = ACCVIFG interrupt pending 08h = BUSIFG interrupt pending (Not present on all devices. See device-specific datasheet)
	Toplevel: <<SYSUNIV {Register}>>
	@