UCSCTL6 {Register}
	Unified Clock System Control 6 Register
	Chapter: 5.4.7
	Table: Table5-9.UCSCTL6 Register Description
	@ XT2DRIVE
		Bit: 15-14
		Type: RW
		Reset: 3h
		Description: The XT2 oscillator current can be adjusted to its drive needs. Initially, it starts with the highest supply current for reliable and quick startup. If needed, user software can reduce the drive strength. 00b = Lowest current consumption. XT2 oscillator operating range is 4 MHz to 8 MHz. 01b = Increased drive strength XT2 oscillator. XT2 oscillator operating range is 8 MHz to 16 MHz. 10b = Increased drive capability XT2 oscillator. XT2 oscillator operating range is 16 MHz to 24 MHz. 11b = Maximum drive capability and maximum current consumption for both XT2 oscillator. XT2 oscillator operating range is 24 MHz to 32 MHz.
	Toplevel: <<UCSCTL6 {Register}>>
	@ XT2BYPASS
		Bit: 12
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: XT2 bypass select 0b = XT2 sourced from external crystal 1b = XT2 sourced from external clock signal
	Toplevel: <<UCSCTL6 {Register}>>
	@ XT2OFF
		Bit: 8
		Type: RW
		Reset: 1h
		Description: Turns off the XT2 oscillator 0b = XT2 is on if XT2 is selected by the port selection and XT2 is not in bypass mode of operation 1b = XT2 is off if it is not used as a source for ACLK, MCLK, or SMCLK or is not used as a reference source required for FLL operation
	Toplevel: <<UCSCTL6 {Register}>>
	@ XT1DRIVE
		Bit: 7-6
		Type: RW
		Reset: 3h
		Description: The XT1 oscillator current can be adjusted to its drive needs. Initially, it starts with the highest supply current for reliable and quick startup. If needed, user software can reduce the drive strength. 00b = Lowest current consumption for XT1 LF mode. XT1 oscillator operating range in HF mode is 4 MHz to 8 MHz. 01b = Increased drive strength for XT1 LF mode. XT1 oscillator operating range in HF mode is 8 MHz to 16 MHz. 10b = Increased drive capability for XT1 LF mode. XT1 oscillator operating range in HF mode is 16 MHz to 24 MHz. 11b = Maximum drive capability and maximum current consumption for XT1 LF mode. XT1 oscillator operating range in HF mode is 24 MHz to 32 MHz.
	Toplevel: <<UCSCTL6 {Register}>>
	@ XTS
		Bit: 5
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: XT1 mode select 0b = Low-frequency mode. XCAP bits define the capacitance at the XIN and XOUT pins. 1b = High-frequency mode. XCAP bits are not used.
	Toplevel: <<UCSCTL6 {Register}>>
	@ XT1BYPASS
		Bit: 4
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: XT1 bypass select 0b = XT1 sourced from external crystal 1b = XT1 sourced from external clock signal
	Toplevel: <<UCSCTL6 {Register}>>
	@ XCAP
		Bit: 3-2
		Type: RW
		Reset: 3h
		Description: Oscillator capacitor selection. These bits select the capacitors applied to the LF crystal or resonator in the LF mode (XTS = 0). The effective capacitance (seen by the crystal) is C(eff) ≈ (C(XIN) + 2 pF) / 2. It is assumed that C(XIN) = C(XOUT) and that a parasitic capacitance of 2 pF is added by the package and the printed circuit board. For details about the typical internal and the effective capacitors, see the device-specific data sheet.
	Toplevel: <<UCSCTL6 {Register}>>
	@ SMCLKOFF
		Bit: 1
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: SMCLK off. This bit turns off the SMCLK. 0b = SMCLK on 1b = SMCLK off
	Toplevel: <<UCSCTL6 {Register}>>
	@ XT1OFF
		Bit: 0
		Type: RW
		Reset: 1h
		Description: XT1 off. This bit turns off the XT1. 0b = XT1 is on if XT1 is selected by the port selection and XT1 is not in bypass mode of operation. 1b = XT1 is off if it is not used as a source for ACLK, MCLK, or SMCLK or is not used as a reference source required for FLL operation.
	Toplevel: <<UCSCTL6 {Register}>>
	@