UCSCTL7 {Register}
	Unified Clock System Control 7 Register
	Chapter: 5.4.8
	Table: Table5-10.UCSCTL7 Register Description
	@ XT2OFFG (1)
		Bit: 3
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: XT2 oscillator fault flag. If this bit is set, the OFIFG flag is also set. XT2OFFG is set if a XT2 fault condition exists. XT2OFFG can be cleared by software. If the XT2 fault condition still remains, XT2OFFG is set. 0b = No fault condition occurred after the last reset. 1b = XT2 fault. An XT2 fault occurred after the last reset.
	Toplevel: <<UCSCTL7 {Register}>>
	@ XT1HFOFFG (1)
		Bit: 2
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: XT1 oscillator fault flag (HF mode). If this bit is set, the OFIFG flag is also set. XT1HFOFFG is set if a XT1 fault condition exists. XT1HFOFFG can be cleared by software. If the XT1 fault condition still remains, XT1HFOFFG is set. 0b = No fault condition occurred after the last reset. 1b = XT1 fault. An XT1 fault occurred after the last reset.
	Toplevel: <<UCSCTL7 {Register}>>
	@ XT1LFOFFG
		Bit: 1
		Type: RW
		Reset: 1h
		Description: XT1 oscillator fault flag (LF mode). If this bit is set, the OFIFG flag is also set. XT1LFOFFG is set if a XT1 fault condition exists. XT1LFOFFG can be cleared by software. If the XT1 fault condition still remains, XT1LFOFFG is set. 0b = No fault condition occurred after the last reset. 1b = XT1 fault (LF mode). A XT1 fault occurred after the last reset.
	Toplevel: <<UCSCTL7 {Register}>>
	@ DCOFFG
		Bit: 0
		Type: RW
		Reset: 1h
		Description: DCO fault flag. If this bit is set, the OFIFG flag is also set. The DCOFFG bit is set if DCO = {0} or DCO = {31}. DCOFFG can be cleared by software. If the DCO fault condition still remains, DCOFFG is set. 0b = No fault condition occurred after the last reset. 1b = DCO fault. A DCO fault occurred after the last reset.
	Toplevel: <<UCSCTL7 {Register}>>
	@