UCSCTL8 {Register}
	Unified Clock System Control 8 Register
	Chapter: 5.4.9
	Table: Table5-11.UCSCTL8 Register Description
	@ MODOSCREQEN
		Bit: 3
		Type: RW
		Reset: 0h
		Description: MODOSC clock request enable. Setting this enables conditional module requests for MODOSC. 0b = MODOSC conditional requests are disabled. 1b = MODOSC conditional requests are enabled.
	Toplevel: <<UCSCTL8 {Register}>>
	@ SMCLKREQEN
		Bit: 2
		Type: RW
		Reset: 1h
		Description: SMCLK clock request enable. Setting this enables conditional module requests for SMCLK 0b = SMCLK conditional requests are disabled. 1b = SMCLK conditional requests are enabled.
	Toplevel: <<UCSCTL8 {Register}>>
	@ MCLKREQEN
		Bit: 1
		Type: RW
		Reset: 1h
		Description: MCLK clock request enable. Setting this enables conditional module requests for MCLK 0b = MCLK conditional requests are disabled. 1b = MCLK conditional requests are enabled.
	Toplevel: <<UCSCTL8 {Register}>>
	@ ACLKREQEN
		Bit: 0
		Type: RW
		Reset: 1h
		Description: ACLK clock request enable. Setting this enables conditional module requests for ACLK 0b = ACLK conditional requests are disabled. 1b = ACLK conditional requests are enabled.
	Toplevel: <<UCSCTL8 {Register}>>
	@